Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-vanvuong-84665452 (LinkedIn) cuibap.xyz (Blog)

Top Skills

Go (Programming Language) PHP Node.js

Certifications

Associate Solutions Architect
Professional Scrum Master™ I (PSM I)

Professional Cloud Architect
Profesional Solutions Architect

Nguyen Van Vuong

Software Engineer

Hanoi

Summary

I worked in FPT for about 5 months then transferred to Framgia Vietnam. At Framgia, I have the opportunity to participate in many projects with roles from Developer to Team leader as well as Brse for Japanese Customers. At Minispace I'm working on myself, and writing articles at https://cuibap.xyz blog.

Experience

Minispace Software Engineer March 2019 - Present (2 years 8 months) https://minispace.xyz

Framgia Inc.
Software Engineer
October 2013 - March 2019 (5 years 6 months)
Hanoi

FPT Software
Bridge System Engineer
May 2013 - September 2013 (5 months)
Hanoi

Education

Ritsumeikan University

Bachelor's degree, Robotic and Computer Vision · (2011 - 2013)

Hanoi University of Science and Technology Bachelor's degree, HEDSPI · (2008 - 2011)

Activity

10/29/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)